sexscanner.com 2012-05-24

# Privacy Policy of SexScanner – Powerful Adult Dating Search Engine

We want to be very clear about what we do with the information we gather from you. This is explained below.

Sometimes our web site may include a link to another site which is outwith our control, and is therefore not covered by our PRIVACY POLICY. While we make reasonable efforts to ensure that any links are properly managed and associated companies have a reasonable and consistent Privacy Policy we cannot guarantee what they may do when you use their web site.

a. Your Information

We will respect your personal information and comply with all applicable UK Data Protection legislation and rules currently in force.

We will use any information provided by you to us to constantly monitor and improve the Services to you and for marketing purposes. We may also use such information to send you specific emails or other related messages which, in our opinion, may be of interest to you in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

b. What information does SexScanner collect?

Registration: When you register with any of our sites, we collect certain data, such as your contact details and demographic information.

When Using the Site: We will keep a record of which areas of the site you are interested in. We also monitor user traffic patterns and Site use.

Competitions and special offers: We may ask you specific questions when you take part in any promotions. If we do, we will keep a record of your answers.

c. What does SexScanner do with this information?

We may use your information in the following ways:

  * to send you information on products or services offered by our company which we think you may be interested in 
  * to notify you about changes to the functionality of our web site
  * to monitor your use of our web site in order to track the volume of traffic on particular pages
  * to share aggregated statistics relating to use of our web site with third parties such as our marketing and business partners
  * to let you know about our service and those products and services of other companies we work with. 

We may also contact you by post, fax, email or telephone.

We may pass the information we collect about you to other members of our group, including companies with which we have joint ventures or strategic alliances. We may also pass your information to carefully selected companies we work with who will use your information for marketing and advertising products and services which may be of interest to you.

>As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, the information we have collected about you will generally be one of the transferred business assets. Also in the unlikely event that SexScanner Search Ltd or its assets are acquired, this information will also be one of the transferred assets.

d. What about "cookies"?

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored on your computer's hard drive by your browser. These allow SexScanner to store your personal information, which we need in order to provide you with the Service. It also allows us to provide features to make your use of any Alcuda Ltd sites easier. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but if you do you will not be able to use all of the features of the Services. If you wish to enable cookies, please follow the instructions below. Take care to ensure that the instructions you select match the type and version of your browser software.

Internet Explorer 8.x:

  * Click on the Tools-menu. 
  * Select Internet Options in the menu - a new window opens.
  * Click on the Privacy tab near the top of the window.
  * Click on the Default button of the window. 
  * Move the slider so that it is on one of the levels below Medium High (including Medium, Low, Accept All Cookies).
  * Save changes by clicking OK. 

Internet Explorer 6.x and 7.x:

  * Click on the Tools-menu.
  * Select Internet Options in the menu - a new window opens.
  * Click on the Privacy tab near the top of the window.
  * Move the slider so that it is on one of the levels below Medium High (including Medium, Low, Accept All Cookies).
  * Save changes by clicking OK.

Mozilla Firefox:

  * Click on the Tools-menu in Mozilla.
  * Click on the Options item in the menu - a new window opens.
  * Click on the Privacy tab. 
  * Expand the Cookies section.
  * Check the Enable cookies and Accept cookies normally checkboxes. 
  * Save changes by clicking OK. 

e. SexScanner Mail

SexScanner mail is our regular 'members only' email that features exclusive discounts and offers as well as a number of reward opportunities. By submitting your email address you are actively agreeing to receive this regular correspondence from us via the email address that you give to us. You can easily unsubscribe or reduce the number of emails you receive from us from any email that we send you or by clicking Unsubscribe option in the mails you receive after signing up.
